We have helped while buying a pretty good plan
coverage, should be 1.5 five seconds gold a
year for you to live, when your boss is late today five
minutes, long no office, year-round remote
work, and people have never been the price.  Wow, I've never heard of it.
Marriage is not a good start, that's right.  While
I love thought they were building a workers’ paradise
, founder DC even said.  It's not that we're particularly generous
, we're actually particularly selfish.  These come to the ground of opening
this later stems from a word pain.  How do you make a person's
death have a meaning, eh, that's why he didn't waste
his life.  From over a share value of the digital empire, to directly
make life, than ten thousand frames, now when it comes to work he rejects
hypocrisy, I am very struggling to see colleagues say our company a big family
, there is really really no
feed.  Feed you busy, on the factory your heart has been officially registered
with Spotify and Apple
Podcast, want to listen to this version of anytime,
click the link below now create your heart D will only
2.0 there, remember to subscribe to the son
2.0.
Welcome to watch your beloved son, we still have a
R left us next door, Nineget
founder, so this episode is actually my
biggest interest is how you manage your team,
how to build a culture, that is, how you can
balance the double industry and the perspective of humanity,
because tomorrow your company I want to earn a lot of money in
Hong Kong.
Relatively not caught up with this kind of such a culture, I want to
understand the logic is what, Hong Kong's
Chinese culture is actually quite back, that is,
with incense I say so, straight culture so that yes next to
OTOT, but there may not be a water
, and then this will be your machine like this, then this
will clear you in your bead station close and then do it
.  So there are many
and not necessarily really depends on the technique your team must be
completely specialized, I look back at the photos, actually, you are
really playing amazing scare right, you have a very high
insurance coverage of such a
benefit can tell us, in fact, that
is what an employee and why in the beginning I would
go to such a recruitment program
Yeah, the spot recruitment program, actually this is our
own direction, that I think this one good company,
dare not succeed a good company, in fact, should
be Pop and um.  In fact, the line of OK followed
that there is after, because I have quite good
people, and take care of your team, in fact, there
will be a frame, not necessarily many, but there must be so of course
this idea is not, from the beginning there is it
.  Let's have a simple box, we call it
LIFL is leafes, that is a pretty good
one ah?  The holiday system, we big price we have
2.5 billion.  Then
pray or take
For example, if I do it in Ninead, then I
want to ask for leave tomorrow, is it my day to ask today can be put,
most of them are the words, usually if you have an emergency
, then not for you, you are not emergency, usually you are a group
will apply for it, I am also very automatic conscious family pet frame, that is,
another name of
your family pet price may see you
Will hire over family price, you don't have to hire an
anuleaf.  Then that we have a holiday,
our holiday and family pet prices are 15 days followed by wedding
prices we have 11, birthdays have 1 day, followed by
leaves on the holidays.  Wow, I've never heard of the
wedding price marriage is very makesense, in fact,
you have a marriage if you will know, in fact, usually called the wedding to
go Yeah so, that is, ten days is equal to the term five, that is five
days so, usually under not tied again, so this
colleague happy, right?  The second one is I,
that is the since.  We have help while buying a
pretty good one of pl્ the coverage should
be 1.55 seconds dollars a year scare, that is, you consider it
120,000 HKD left there, so to speak, funny d is your birth
time frame, basically we will help while buying live
insurance.  That is, if at the same time unfortunate
life, basically there is money is given to his family frame, so
Junior while we have five years of salary in his
coverage.  At the same time we have ten years of salary it
coverage followed by the F is it, that
is, salary, commission,
I think the topofthemarket or at
least the middle and upper system market, followed by the last E
, E I think actually to yet, actually is the
empat, that sometimes some places do not build that category
frame, how you can have a so-called reply to your heart
.  Those frameworks you just mentioned are regulations, or still
yes, yourself you yourself will be anyway so we
LIF there are all regulations, that is, I think
sometimes you do not write out we do not believe it, write out we
feel fed, you said it, you have to do it.
Hey, I'm a very, very typical ring color field out there
.  Um so well, my perspective is certainly that feed, the square of the
incoming is what the number is, how can give us more advantages
, your perspective, how do you serve that person?  My
perspective is as typical as you, basically we won't hire you
, we are more of a fly-by-wire type of company.  So, but I
mean I if I'm a boss outside,
is that
lie a feed, we must be everything to continue the frame, is that
too, fate wash do, really have back so up and down the age,
but not I think the point is what?  On we sometimes think
sweep, we do these so-called favorable facilities measures
are not actually us particularly generous, in fact, we are particularly selfish
.  Yes we really want to do the position is that we can retain some
people, and thus the company is even better.  You if you do a company do a
actually you will find.  Talent of staying this, with
wages to flow this is the most.  Because for example, if you meet, then he asks
you how much you want the job to cost you ten thousand dollars I match you and
add 20% frame so your thinking this is more people.  But I
tell you this company has such a holiday, with
insurance outside the company, it will not
match the because it matches the whole
company to change.  In fact, we think that covering people with these,
is actually the most powerful way to come, especially to choose the person, in fact,
he is really a person called automatic conscious yeah, he knows
what he wants.  What is it about you that you feel suddenly to
this is not already so collapsed from the beginning?  Hello, at the beginning
, you will try something to feed, foreign companies have a
lot of interesting practices right, can not try, because after all we have
gone to those entrepreneurial programs in the United States, we are constantly
looking at some good foreign companies, in fact, they try some
practices.  model are after which other
company's affairs country.  That I personally like a company called
base, which is the company, actually its a
studio called signal it, they have a lot of
very unique management company culture of something to write.  Also
sometimes we will watch Netflix, no
, that watch Netflix on etlix the company
noRoseroll is two, that I thought those
writical those are our own think
wow, great, but we tried ourselves after realizing
that you can not just move foreign practices, sometimes you have to do some
localization
fast.  I wonder, because
actually our current company this and is and what will become of
nothing?  Usually based on what books I read recently,
yes yes, this I absolutely white is me, I
read the noRules
Ruletlix book a year or two earlier, then read the
rela and said to the company, can not feed, we now
all speak new words, is following us now d, we
will slowly spend six months?  Go over to
model the look, actually in the middle of this I see, in fact,
it has its theoretical benefits yes so but in fact in the middle I
think implement up when there will
be some bits in place, how you are going or in your early days
, there are no which bits, you are that you are not wrong
.  However, in the case of Hong Kong this has to be
implemented like this.  The so-called keep trying to keep
learning so that something in the right direction, the
execution may not always work that I think this one
and that society and that culture, that is the so-called that work
DNA is actually very different, that is very related
.  We can see, for example, we just mentioned you said infinitely large
frame so, we about so 7 or eight years ago actually I have
tried it, at that time the most seen the data is the
more advanced while the more courageous frame, the more at the same time the less
enough to ask for leave, because he will think that if I ask for a price, then
I will feel like it is unavailable, I hire a good one - that is, I ca
n't actually work
, but this, he will feel feed, I do not according to you ű
what that means you understand, that this position will do a such a
called change appears, so and I this very large
position is some while he refuses, but he thinks the station you
, he will feel scared out of the ji, you guys, you must
write down the paper behind me think, then
you draw and say no
The one who owes, one image is the Lord.  When you say the
word employer, what comes to mind?  What adjective
conscientious owner, have thought of the conscientious employer that, in fact, I think
must be a minority, so I consider you Default is me
because of the thought when, in fact, no one began to anyone to dart
, in fact, you are like the epidemic water line so it is more difficult.  Yeah
break this technique from the impression, because I, I have in the early days to
speak to us, ah you as you please up and put home
do not put it, I trust you you arrange your own work your own
arrangement, the first six months?  No one actually
executes this one thing.  I think it's
whether everyone hangs out like me, or how.  It was until almost six months a
month to yeah, then we have a new writer
he just joined the job, because we
interview with him said, we
have such a police, he has actually become the
first to implement the same, in fact, I have said six months earlier, we
do more of these things, I trust everyone
's things, then slowly I noticed ah, everyone will start to
do this.  It's very reasonable, I think it
's very difficult to turn around from the old way, which is equivalent to
you having to chase the tired boy, itself not angry for a long time, you tell him you
are a good man, it's hard to go smoothly, because he thought
, my friend you so long, do not know how how a scumbag so
, but you a new girl, you pretend you are
a good person, not scumbag, in fact,  What about the stories
?  How can you hit them that maybe for
not being able to trust that fear, I think we and we closed
later fixed it, just now you see our holidays, in
fact, we have changed there is a limit, yes, that
I probably have more than 20 days frame, but we have
other things to do, is to finish after you do not look back at the data
exactly what we need to feed, in fact
How much to first we will think back, in fact, fake you have to wear today
's things, in fact, how much you need at most or
average how much this is the first step, the second
part is you really execute to come that I think the company, for example,
you say the boss often sit in the company, then you
say fromhome, in fact, he does not believe you,
we were at that time, that is,
before we covid.  We have already said that we can work
from home, no one works
fromhome, because all your companies those
so-called bosses 9 o'clock finally sitting in the company right, so yours at the
same time where so, until covid we are afraid to death,
before workfromhome, then we
incidentally or calloffice do not
buy, so now we are basically a hundred, in fact, you
do these measures the goal, is it?  In fact, the
house and the wat, that is not important that is
focuson the performance
, not the focus on the presence
.  In fact, as long as you can do that why, in fact, that
technique does not have to copy foreign countries, or copy any
company.  So what about that from measure you have now
?  That is unlimited, right, you do not rent the place,
every day can not actually have actually just earlier I said very like to read
a book, that the company called base
campe, his book called work, in fact, the
correct saying is not fromhome, you
can, you can, you go to the working or go to
coffee or not.  To add actually the point, we have to
understand the bit is, in fact,
not necessary.  In fact, you need to make an appointment at the same time out to meet,
there is a need to see it, there is an office and very work
put, you know, in fact, is not a perfect way to come,
even if you say the world most need in the office of the job
, is always actually the person may go out to meet, he is not the
office, that is because of fault that
is something, that is, our own company eighty percent of the
work, in fact, do not need to do
To, so good back two percent of us out to meet yeah, a lot of
working already, for whatever every
street level while actually having its flexibility there to
match the scare, you have to hire someone who knows themselves so
what you want, that is, for example, when we go to meet, in fact, we never
ask if there is a release, after all, this is something very few people will
ask Jur.  More is, you ask very put experience
, in fact, what he wants, that maybe he is good, or
actually he has children to take care of, or the family has parents to
take care of, that is actually to ask him exactly what his position is
, purely want to be lazy, or actually because there is a need
, yes, so I would think that I do not think
workfromhome or remote
is the working model.  But I think this is the right
working model for our own company.  At the same time, the people we are looking for also have to
find some people who are suitable for us.  If eh now
I hear, wow these companies can put completely
remote work, so there is a certain characteristics of
people your team can maintain it, then you will
fish which few things yes this person is suitable
.  I think to find those people, in fact, he to himself is already called
more automatic and conscious, OK.  Automatically in whether he knows what
he wants here, that is, we ask for
example, feed you for the next three months, and if you start these
jobs, actually you will want to do something, feed you the
plan for the rest of your life, that is, if he says no,
in fact, this is very worrying.  That is because that means you have to help me
.  Yes, and if not, a month
later he still asks you, what can I do in my career ah
this position, I think it takes that person to know what they want
.  Is there some that interview you
will go for the ideal you want, and to set some
quality.  You will design something that
can make it after he answered you, you will know the answer so
this one line automatically, you will be better than asking him what you want to do except asking him what you want to do
.  Maybe sometimes some
technical positions
actually you will send some rets to him.  Get him to hand at the
end, he usually may not be good, OK? Because
just said automatically conscious that thing is actually feeding, you have to tell
you to tell you at the same time what you did ah, usually
these people his characteristic is actually you let tas let him discover
done him, and tell you he did.  Even if Master Mori hasn't done it yet
, he'll tell you that I haven't done it yet.
Exactly, that I think you have to over
commun's, actually this thing.  First,
second is for example, we hire people process, we try to
team, in fact, we hire a person is I asked him
not OK, in fact, he said OK, so those are usually not
cheap, that we often really have a
principle, is the penalty, is that want to do
not do it, that is, I usually usually a company,
colleagues, you usually hire less.
So why so many companies economic bad to money, our
company 18 years ago never for economic reasons, in fact,
not because we have a lot of money, in our hiring
we are very careful, such as a colleague, scare, we
Default not, wow, we have to feel
back not, I think because support more do
these things the year should take less time to do more things
.  Um, not you or auto not left, so
changed, in fact, you do not need to immediately return to the
position, you see at the same time, exactly
how unsupportable, that is, we always say,
higher when you feel
ping, is it really painful right
To think about it, this I think is the most difficult part is that he can not or what
he wants, in fact, he told you earlier, OK? The
situation is equivalent to the relationship between boyfriend and girlfriend or parents and children, you have to
say it?  I'm actually afraid of the bit is and dead looking
.  Yours is usually that he wants to hold it
that I think the best position is to have time to say doing not quite
happy right, is it better not to tell me, directly tell
the manager, he is not happy to do this he thinks the
company is not going to help him.  Assist him together to find a direction
, he thinks we stabilize the back of the mind before I have to break up
, especially when the colleague at first not have a trust
, in fact, he needs some time, yes, that is so
you left the good words, should be when you accumulate or
we late retreat you, you should not
surprise, yes, this is very important
.  OK?Hold communication it, and automatic conscious it, is
there still it?  That if it's really, wow, well can be very goal-
based, I goal-based some OK.  What does it look like when it’s goal-based
?  Goal-based is it always required you to give some
checkpoint to him, that is,
tell you yes, then to always hold the hand to do things,
so but you know often when the company is not large, in fact, basically
feed, you did out of it, in fact, how you
do is not the point of it, to give more than one person
to automatically conscious it is not necessarily
responsible for what you usually feel automatically
White frame he talks will not be a bit, you hear you and things know
him, he is not goal-based job interview, we know how to
pretend to be goal-based, this this I think there is one thing in Hong Kong is that
since the beginning, we already know how to
interview, that is basically false
?  That is so I think instead you are well that person we all
feel OK want to hire followed then so you actually in the
first few months, actually you hand
holding to do more when to tell you
what the culture of our company is, and I think our
own approach is when we meet, I have said to feed actually
everyone equal relationship you choose I choose you things you choose I
am the same, you do not think I do
I tell you, you do not need to be unhappy, we very
focus that position is I do not have to make you the public exactly what
else do?  Because let you hear what I am like, you may not
necessarily change me, but the same guide you, I will tell you
I will want what, so you have a hold communication
when, in fact, slow eyes you find more than a group of called more fit the
colleague, so our accumulation rate is low
Almost right, then D has to have other things to think about how to
push this.  Well, you guys fromhome
, have there or so, I guess there are a lot of that is, have there been
, how do you usually structure a week
.  We each team
actually they have their own arrangement of, we consider less
distributed, um so the way of doing, that
we, for example, I and I direct ing several
teams
and how many one
so 6 seven one side has 6 seven, well this is we
have the so-called twopiezaroom, that is,
this horse believes he said feed, actually hold a meeting, add you to buy
2 too many, actually not enough za.
Because usually that will, everyone is in the color pretending to
type, followed by actually WhatsApping
, so those places that is too many people my people if it is
so needed, you do not he stay there do not need to
leave, the biggest cost of starting a company, I am very meeting
, although at the same time to find open.  Once said yeah, he
thinks, if you don't so Val do a stop then he
came to open it, that you may leave and then perform
other work still have value, you just sit there.  This is
certain, actually you calculate back to know, a person, I think
I do not know how much money he is convenient I consider him 30,000 dollars company
, that is, every day the company gives 1000 dollars to him a
day I consider to go back 8 hours to 10 hours to provide, in fact,
he is here every hour
D money ordered him, is it the first to do this?  And
his colleague and feel like nothing, satisfied so well, so
these we try to avoid, often to.  Feed this is not
necessary to open the frame, that is some so-called routine, that is why to open I
do not know, those things usually you are the easiest to have problems
those constantly ask this is not possible, this needs to be framed
, do not let your own frame is framed.  This is what
you mean by goal-based, this will have no purpose
first.  Yes, but good.  Everyone, after all, you hire people back this
in fact, new people are easy to be with, that is,
like your cover up so your color darker will cover up
will cover you have such a leak, the body of the person no matter how much he
progress or, or open, will be
affected here, so these we constantly have to mention ourselves
is fed, I have to say at the same time, feed, you do
not feel right to tell us what I do not know.
Please don't let everyone join us so soon.  How many people are there in your current company
?  We different companies bury me maybe 70 people there
, you are seeing a person who comes in on your own, you are still
distributed but at the same time there are seen scares, usually see that position
, in fact, I make sure that person is not.  How does that
mean I told you, feed us to talk,
actually I'm not inter, just want to, choose to come
, I'm five minutes ten minutes ah Okay, I have no problem,
thank you all, that will have these, but not much,
because my colleagues actually know what we want people
, scared yes, usually those places
I will not want to feed you because I don't want to go to this position
For many people, he may be tasked with meeting people and hiring
people.  You have actually just mentioned that we are all
good interview, in fact, there are many
typical questions, typical answers we have pr sun swing
those questions that is, your biggest
taboo from the answer to an interview you are to
get to know each other, but because people have prep all the
time, you do not have the opportunity to recognize, you will not
redesign all your questions yeah, there are some
questions that you can be different from the west or rise
When the real thing comes back, see some when, generous is
we do not necessarily ask, very vain ườ wonderful things of, in fact,
we ask you back to the past scare, whether there are some projects is
you do it, you must be from zero to one how to do, from one
to 10 o'clock to do it, your character ah we are afraid of that position is
good, so-called
old while not talking
Say, because my own view is that you make yourself a ya
.  That is, not in doing unhappy for leaving, is it the first to leave you
do not need to keep for him to harm you.  Working in a company
especially a start-up company actually you choose the problem right, you often consider
yourself a victim, you will not be willing to change right, does that mean
you will not feedback right, so this is
not what we want people.  How would you ask if
the person I'm seeing right now is a very
accountable person
.  Ask directly, what examples does he have.  Oh, you said
ask him directly if.  No I have not asked, do you think you
consider yourself a very complicated person?  So of course it is
, so what about most of the things I gave an example of
?  That is, for example, I ask you, ah boy, actually this
content how to do it huh, actually you have 90,000
examples said out of it, that is, you do not just stop in
a highlevel, is to talk about darts of the position
, you really have substantial real people really bloody things like things to
share it, that is, all people who can do it
will experience your things.  I think your relationship
can all get a good story? This means that
even if you see a lot of people come will be wrong,
because it is the saying
basically everyone is very la, used to be more of a loss
, yes, now instead I think it's
you, you tell him the culture of public, he thought he could take over
, but in fact he may not be able to
break up.  Yes.  Yeah, now I find out,
I'm in the interview is a set,
because our company is doing Autonomy great
autonomy, but at the same time some people will think wow, great right cool right
so big you are not unhappy, photos are
back so high, may give you outside know so many companies
higher card down, do you really stand up?  So I even
in the interview there, I will try to
scare him, actually not shoot me to tell him the facts, so that he
has a correct actually we here is not that sometimes I d
sharing yeah, share yeah, he sometimes for example,
hear we say so-called profit, feed, how can you install your
sister-in-law is everyone saying this is the words, but the problem feed
us do you do something short of goods?  Is it
delivery, which means that is how we do things.  In the past
, we wanted to copy those very successful companies, copy their
practices, but now we often instead tell you,
I tell you what kind of person I am, then at the same time
you better tell me what kind of person you are, we do
not work together, not fit we think about how to think about the
next step, and sometimes I think there is some incompatibility, that is not going to do  To be
honest, we have space to adjust.  It's the same thing
you communicate, basically most of the work
is actually there, that can not be solved, I do not catch him all the way
letter wind is not first or even sometimes actually he said he wanted to switch to a
row right our company does not have this vacancy so I asked the new which
friends company really recommended some good while recommending him
said not like not you do better D large organizations on you
make him better that friend so you
You and he are not in your department, that's not how we
play, yeah.  This should be through many
breakups will be able to claim it, how many times have you proposed
breakups so say when so your company hires people to meet people you lie may have met
thousands of people, in fact, you will not remember those unhappy
things.  Instead, I think it's remember some happy things,
you ask me who is good at the same time can do things, I immediately up
a notoriety for you to hear, but do not remember do not remember those
how can remember it, that is, for your wife asked you how good you have in the past
to make you impression of men forget women, did not remember to care, right?
I wonder, in fact, you each still have the first time to
break up Yeah huh so at that time this for you to see how it is
usually very bad, that is, there is a chance to be able to
do something from those materials, for example, I remember well that we felt that
some colleagues were actually not very suitable for us.  Then we choose an
unreasonable time, that is the time ah is some before and after Christmas
, oh scare, that we were wanting to believe that pattern is
for, there is a problem to quickly crisply solve it, because
we have several positions, is the person is not suitable for your company,
in fact, he changed jobs earlier, in fact, for him is a good
thing.  That is, we only think of the high
level of good um but did not think of the position is
actually some human stories are to deal with it, you do not
Christmas, you do not around the New Year is not enough experience, so
lucky those colleagues at that time.  There are some actually they have grown up
mature, in fact, we are OK, sometimes the street
hit is OK, that is, these are very lucky,
you know do or become the company's executives, you you have done
too down this position, you look at the information we are people to ha, that is
not that we are not people look, in fact, everyone is a lot of
feelings there are many places in the family has a challenge, that is, his mother is not good,
that is, his mother is not a challenge
, so he can not 100% of the work, that is, these
people brought more experiences lost more, you will be with your heart
more, but when you were young no ah, his done do not
fire, is it necessarily so, but the will not be, in
fact, I recently this is actually an interview
, because we overprap, so you
can not ask the
function itself is
Well, that is actually something you need to know,
how can I design it to be a you don't know I'm asking this
, but I'm back to being a is you answered you don't know, I would wonder if there will
be some specific questions in Nine's interview
, I share the next one I myself
, a friend to teach me.  I ask you if you are
a passionate person, who would say no
.  But if I ask that there is something in this world
you do not like, you see you will leak, you
will sleep not smell so a person says no ah I'm cheap right, I'm good nothing
sign him nothing is going to touch him, nothing
moves him he may not necessarily be too
anything.  But if that's the one thing I like the most
, then you'll oh start to be able to meet this
one person, are there any special
questions like that that you can share.
I think a
person, his negative emotions may not be his positive
emotions that thing similar, I think not necessarily, some people good
life does not mean that the life for these things you want him to do
he is very positive not necessarily actually because I think often is annoyed,
derived from your
inability to change a sense of powerlessness
Many times he will try to change, so that he can change
, in fact, he may not be so angry, because he thinks that
for example, I have two dogs, yes, I like small
animals, so but for example, restraints, actually I will not
especially for this, because I will report to the police to arrest him, that is, I think
this is not solved actually like, I think I used to read this novel, I think I used to
read this novel, I think I used to read this novel
If there is, who do you like to watch people the most, you
can TV can what must be really reading books, but we will think
we can ask him whether he actually read books, first financial
novels have not read, in fact, for this one Hong Kong people
so much, I think so, or at least watch graphic dramas
.  Well, it turns out that it is, and it depends on how to use it, followed by the
second is what characters he chooses, actually reflecting what he wants to be
a what character 囉
Filming ah, ah what the show is good to see, on the one hand you
want to say to people I'm good everyone, so that we
talk, the aspect through watching movies know what it is.  Feeding
, in fact, is actually exactly want to achieve this
kind of function yeah, is through the daily life of your
habits your time will put aside your thinking
and extract to exactly what you are a.  Yes, there are
studies showing this that is, for example, in the past, very popular to say
Google people this ask you, do you know
how many channels in Hong Kong, that ask a d, very jump you from those things, but
later this after a few years after I think 10 years later
said, Google found this kind of hiring, in fact, with
his company success is not directly related, sometimes
really see how to borrow and sometimes I think
I want to know, for example, your
head finance question yeah he answer will react that for example, for example, when
I was in college I answered
I like Hu Wucong Of course, his life is not extreme, but
he is very stupid, then martial arts is very strong, then finally obtained the beauty
home, yes, then lived a lot of life, this is a
situation I want and doing
Voted down, so somehow on the reaction to this character, that is,
there is a person he comes, he thinks his favorite person is Wei
Xiaobao, eh, so you have to be careful, are your colleagues
dating d oh actually have to have to have to think review
.  I quite believe that no one will say that they like Wei Shao Bao, except for the
public and I am in finance. You say that people should not like Wei Shao
Bao.  If I like Joe, I'm reflecting my star.  Bi
, I think, right, that I will intuitively be the fly drama
hero question, I always ask, to the whole
conversation is very pocket frame, is
I will ask you what is the biggest mistake in life ha, you
want to check me enough?  This is one of the
reasons, the second thing is what exactly is the challenge you encounter,
scare, that you do not have enough reil and follow the next
question asking you so how do you get out of this challenge?  That is false
If the he just says oh, my public snow above very benefited bent
囉, I will think your life is too
concerned exactly at the same time his that that resistance to mineral pressure how high
.  Oh he did not go through ści, yes, you will see that is that
if he is most in
poorer grades, or work has some grievances or let people
talk about it.  Yes, so these you know that this person really did
not experience the wind no, not necessarily not ah, but that
I think this position is not enough, and the other side of the photo
he was able to tell you well that he is an honest
person so it becomes you will feel that you can actually add heart and and
another we are now doing more is so-called.  That
is suppose that person, because we do the company a more people.   There
are always some people, in fact, he has been a friend of a friend company so big
how do you say ask it, see that person he will give what
comment?  If it is very senior, he does not know
, then he does not ask his colleagues, because usually the person left
you ask him back actually he does not mind talking, but the person he
said great so OK usually false ეთ
I
have a lot of friends around me, actually very cheat, they are
at work is management
level, in fact, under them may have some people really
do not perform,
um.  And did not perform for a long time, and did not
see any bends and turns, but they will
keep keeping his but I wonder, in
fact, if there is a right person to step in, he actually knows he has to
deal with but he does not know.  Do you have some so say to him
, how it is actually done.  I think first to try to take the
first step to talk to you first.  That is understanding that he should not
perform because you did not give
him a clear instruction, because I think this is very used to the situation is
how is success you did not give a definition to the colleague.
So don't cut off so quickly the other person asks first this into this is the
first step the first step is that you ask, in fact, what do you think I
have improved myself, how can I help you do better?  Scared,
that is often the loser this often talk to at the same time, I
think not empower colleagues, in fact, instead
to turn is unlock flip his
potential out, well emp is
itself like this, you add a, add a add a rocket to him like this
, but actually choose some to say you do not listen to me how to help you,
how to help you unlock usually help is talking about
coaching or what?  A lot of times, I
think it would say, is it actually not clear enough, so you don't know what
I want, scaring or feeding wouldn't actually be the
job, everyone that category isn't what you're best at?
That I think you are asking, after asking him some people falsely answer him
really intend to work, he will hope to tell you,
and sometimes I will feel as a leader especially now
, I want Jesus that I will feel more and more is a kind of
just so-called leadership, that you
do not feel superior.  You the other think is I
as taste, I as the master how to help you do well, strictly says
you have to do your part, if you can do it is what you
directreport he was able to do happy unhappy better or
worse, he was able to talk to you.  I
think this one is the first step to success but what about this one
, not everyone will default to think that way
.  That's good, then we do hire some good people, is not the
world is good, so you are very difficult, is it a prophet that for example,
we say we have the benefits, we do our own practice, my
goal is not to want the whole world of companies to follow us oh, is it the first do not
follow, exactly and I think sometimes a
position is you think that is the best, but actually some
people tell me really do not want to
work
Grind it
.  That is, some people are like that, so people are so choice
life is him and not wrong, because life is not you, that
I think this position is bigger than I think not hiring
some good or bad colleagues, is some know unsuitable colleagues
not fit not fit not not good or
badfit not fit
Team flavor, that's it.  Just now you have said two
steps, the first is, in fact, have you talked about giving to hear
a substantive standard, what does it look like to do well.  The second
part is you tell him, is there anything I can do to help you
, in fact, the third part, you said, he won't be.
Because you have already made it clear.  Yes, I have seen some of our
teams before the highest is to make a colleague, he
chooses his own profit, and time also very grateful to you.  Give
him a careeradvise.  That is, I think
this is the highest level, that is, you say you want to worship
him, but he is worshiping himself and thank you very much for me to be able to
make this first step of this determination, I this is very high level,
that is, I do not dare to say that I do one time, but I am
I think this is good, but sometimes I think for example,
you dating breakup happy shooting will not break up, but
you will not break up
Before, in fact, we should have good communication, thereby you will not
have a regret.  And aborting the breakup is fine, really fine
, the most worthy of celebration is that hey, this one is his own
choice.  Not obviously actually must be to
him will his own choice, is the best is not chosen
or being chosen so it is usually unhappy so no so
, but this I would think it is negotiable, that you sometimes
your company while accumulating your that while very important hold actually you are
not happy, no we are lucky to do things together doing things, everyone can do something
, but I feel grateful
Well the position, would it be either something happy so it would be
even better.  In a so many environments down the system,
so we are fat or are there cheat arch frame this is
lineable, that is fat talking about the communication can
be fat that no matter how high-level or low-level you are, you directly
find an attempt to communicate, I think the comm is,
when you have to work, there must be a different
street level, what is the point?  Because of what
you’re at, you’re senior, so you’re able to take charge
.  Or build a Chinese society, we misunderstand that, high-
level like the King of Heavenly Father, so I can point you to work
, but actually not, I think it's high-level because you are
responsible.  So you are able to have the power, because if anything is not
possible I ask you.  I think this position is where we have this
, in fact, we have to understand this.  I want to
understand that this is not one, I think.  Not a
grown up in Hong Kong out of nowhere a come how do you go
fine what is called what responsibility?  Usually that time is
that category, he is the most, usually that colleague actually
he will be easier to make a good decision so you give the
responsibility is often able to make a good decision while,
so give the responsibility, that is, in ordinary terms is, in
fact, the colleague is not promoted, right?  But often
we will understand that some people are very la
individual
contributor but not necessarily a leer from the leer
actually his
technicalskill is not very
high, but he really knows, intimidating people, that you
understand that I think we often misunderstood that personal things done
must be a good leader.  Because out there big
in this standard most of the higher it rises, usually the more expensive that is the
reason, yes, so I think this is a
situation that will appear in very large institutions Yeah, so this
we as the world company, we can eh called it.  You
notice the most player team leader in the
company, of communication is
different from out, that is actually he is very very proactive very strong
, that is ਭਾਈ say he can, what things have to appear
, he dare not send you, he means he has the opportunity he
has to discuss with you, I know he got it himself.  So if
people live here and you say ah, we have to do this, does that count
as him helping you solve the problem?  My best is that he can give it
to us, but this is living with different ages doing the
company left this I have fixed it.  When I was young, I
was talking about the time when the company just started, please
come back to solve the problem, you talk about the problem out please
give a solution, it used to be like this.  So that way
this actually we will not point out the problem frame,
because he is a good thing to think of me, so he does not even say the question,
that is now to go back to the place you say the problem is fine, but
if you can give the eh, I think this is so
can be with a may be able to often spend problems, the colleague
so he wow you did a good job.  Better I have higher
requirements for you can tell me, in fact, if you come how will
solve it, for the society is a training, is a
levelup, that is, I think the company
you are not sololevel, you are
together to levelup, you are very difficult.  Yes you had to be
strong, can not that you watch football
wear a very strong striker, that is full of taste actually, a
we are quite important, are often we and its company the same
no, I am very fighting while saying that our company a
big family, that is not a building, really really no, why can be
explained, big family this statement what's wrong.  The big family
statement, the problem is that you don't do well.  I am
able to worship you, that can be fired,
exactly that I think this is not, and
you this is lying, is it first you tell him, we
once that is able to tolerate each other, right, your mother,
or this child mirror so cheap still love him, and we
understand why some people will use
everyone to say ah, to help, is for the sake of the legacy
A sense of belonging like that so if I really wanted to be straight,
do the genus, but did not want to be dishonest how would you go.
I just said directly, everyone listen, we are a team like this
, we go together to win the game, in the market I find a
good player to do this position, and we will continue to
think together how to make up for this game, is I think this
is quite important, and this thing really needs to be said
, because to be honest, you may not be in this position  It's
not so much for you outside is a bad colleague, so
your position is changed to everyone because we can mature, so very
good, can tell what they have what is good and what is not
good, how can take a responsibility, children are no longer responsible
, adults can not, so I just invite the adults
back, sometimes the age brought to business just stop,
in fact, stay in the children
.  I hear now that it's actually very elite, in your company
, we have to topsalartopof
themarket, and then hire the most capable
people, that is, players from, so we are
not a big family, we mean if you drive will
not థ, we are completely using
oriented things.  I want to know actually in the early days
you become such a model company before this appeared
some bad characteristics, such as politics
ah, whether there, because not running this set, there have been
some problems.  That ್ದਉਂ, but the first one is actually that
is your culture, actually your approach,
you do not talk about very high, very high-level line,
and do not know how to connect and flourish, but you live to deserve to receive money so
this is.  Um your culture is fake, isn’t it?  But
your approach is actually your culture, so this first
point, the second I quite believe in the culture of a company, in fact, the
founder, or the leadership, or the
seniorleader that character of the extension of, that
is, you do not go to engage in politics, in fact, the
company is some framework, that is, I think people do not know how to do
, in fact, because he has some bad
experience
This, I have to do a mountainism, and have to collect like this.  In
fact, these are said not to hear, he actually we do not thing, but I
think quite important position on how
to be happy, say, we are not to things and not
people, we are all ICBC, I think this is everyone is like it
.  What if there is an audience for this show?  They are also
management level he needs
, he knows there are some problems in the team he needs to
conduct a hard
conversation, and he himself,
may not necessarily want so often will form a drag frame right, drag first
, see if it is wrong, see if the problem will not naturally
lose, and then in the head actually must not, but
the egg will be higher and higher can tips it or what can you do
I would think so for example, we do the company in 18 years
.  I have never been a late colleague or colleague.  In fact, later
regret, you have that thing, actually able to make you feel that to tell
him, to return him late, in fact, I think that thing is already
very hurt you usually work there so you
tell him, that is like a fish inserted in your teeth, that is, that is the
bone so you come out, in fact, even if you bleed
, in fact, you will not be comfortable
The, that is not wrong can not be not can not be wrong
so at the same time you need to tell you
actually I need you, that I think doing a company for being a
person is often a good thing put on the same thing, that
is equivalent to some people say that the company to be bold,
feed, worship a contrast of things  The
company actually tends to be like this, that is, first you see we say
very automatic angle very demanding, the other side of the photo I try to is
I am to the same time good, I am teamfirst of
we have a certain interest eh so system changed maybe you can
find an interesting mix, OK oh, and we
have a pretty interesting, quite interesting one to come, is
you I, we will give you the 100,000 dollars in cash
.  Yes, we are in the Hong Kong government photo,
yes, encourage colleagues to have children so, our view is
because so I'm too child, scared so, I think, wow
your child your public hospital Hong Kong, of course, public health care is good
so, but fake
Ga, you want more options, I said actually very high
is it possible to get it?  In fact, the starting point actually comes we
think is
and in the meantime he does 10 years so, we will give a
year's salary distance as a bonus.  Why would you
open a suit like this?  In fact, some of the feelings of good times people so
scare, that is when I was at the end of 100 years when I brought
birth health followed by bringing him a week after, he was infected so
, followed by the hospital he he two months followed by the end, his
time passed so that period was the lowest point in life, yes.
Then after that I played for about 3 months of this, then did not return to
work.  Then that is thinking about the meaning of life like that.  When
I go back to the company I will think, fake if the child is not a
child, and a colleague whether colleagues can have me like this
called next, is can not need to think about work things is
can concentrate on as scheduled, if it is really unfortunate, the deceased that
is a colleague, then I as a company I exactly
how long to give the colleague out, that is, these are actually a lot of my children's problems
, so but how to turn this fortune into a one
blessing to others.  So in the company why do it out, in
fact, this is that opportunity, yes.  How
can you that is turn it, that Qualcomm how much thinking ah how
many old rules so, first of course is my wife, in fact,
we are together and walking, is it just a child born, those
they call what in have not sat all, right, he has to go to
visit him, Leung couples car together experienced that position is very
important, followed around the time
I believe, followed by my wife
I think the power of faith is also huge, everyone dies, yes
, but how do you make a person's death have a
meaning and eh this thing is.  He did not waste his life
, so you see often some people, he such as him, do
some parents leave him, does it mean that they leave his
gacyplan may part of them go to their own previous
institutions, in fact, the same reason, but this time we are called
unlucky, the son died before us so, how we can
turn this thing, is is called entrepreneurship itself
, I think this must be meaningful and entrepreneurship itself
Yes, that always you are a comparison
person, wearing these things you solve so but you seek and with
time how to make this matter rich the meaning, are we
luck do the position, of course, it seems very quiet
analysis, in fact, not I think are all aspects of the test
hate things.  I believe that in fact, you say in
business you start a company, you will encounter
some obstacles of course, may really
think about thinking of ways to solve it, but there are some really like
you just said the pain of words in fact there are many, difficult times
, and I believe also you as an
entrepreneur you will definitely have some
high and low experience of ji, you will feel that if this is a
hard tim people watching this
, you may be on your own private or in the company
when you encounter obstacles, what ways can, can return to
yourself.  I will not think back is zoin and
zoom Europe think, that is, in experiencing life challenges
, you zoom
10 years later look back even more, equal to childhood we
study that I and you, I believe we are back to an era
, will not be able to take the exam in the world right, nowadays you ask back
and Whocares?
question, actually not a big problem.  So the position is feeding
, you now have a success, have a very happy position zo, is it
enjoy that moment, and at the same time you are very grateful so your
zoominzoom really looks like a camera, so
you do not make you wear life these ugly unhappy things, in
fact, you will not feel so disgusting.  I have just peeked at your you there
above, in fact, you have read the books,
in fact, I see your tendency, that is, although you have religious beliefs
driven at the same time and time this and will look at good things, that is, when the time
or the average person will think about these two things
, religion and a way of thinking of your own, seems to be good
back, but in you and law, it seems that there is no conflict
right.  I think there is actually no
one aspect of life you still have to make your own efforts so the
situation is equivalent to when you go to work, in fact, your colleague chooses the
boss, like
for example, I believe in Jesus.  I know God is watching, I know
whether you can or can not actually he has his, you have
a feeling like knowing weight, that is, you have a brain, that
you know for example while he can not write you know me, in fact, I find
will help me solve, so this thing is actually not rushing
scare, and moreover the position is for some good people to
see, in fact, this thing is more important to see
A testimony of Mr. Jin, my of course very good, that
he does not know is the young president of Rock Greater China is not
?  Then he was the Treasurer, then he had to step down due to some
other events, followed by a lot of life's challenges
.  He said that many times in this society, he has to think that he must
solve so, yes, so but he wants Jesus after
he found that there is a big guy, is I can hand over to the big
guy, so there is handed over to the brain does not mean you act,
do not work hard, because the brain has a task for you, but he
will walk with you.  That is equivalent to you going to exercise,
someone from the side looking at you you are not good, not very afraid of getting
hurt you are not very afraid actually you will be there You
signed a contract with you when you were a child
㖞 So now you are also taking care of the children so, you
will plan to put this when your son is quite old so that he
on Instagram those social media to see the road so follow the
education contact
AI yeah, you still insist, he has to be far away from you spelling, wow,
deepquestion, you think nervous about the ultimate
parenting yeah this is yeah, your attitude
.  Me, I’ll be quite interesting and I’ll share my own experience
.  Actually I uh, primary school to secondary school results are quite good, that
is, I will take the exam to record such, but study to university when
studying the same, I will recall, is when I was a child
, he built under your management, in fact, your
hands yeah those things, so that you can be more base d
, so that you can be to hand rules, but it is the same time to fly I will
fly
In fact, you will be the middle pole no that section no lift, the middle pole no yeah, that
is, if you that not angry are very rules, followed by the
university you live abbreviations when, you do not have to go home.
Then after that you become the day playing video games, and not studying
, that is, the high level changed, you say give no good.  In fact, it will be
even worse once it rebounds.  That's me, so I
think a lot now that it was you who told you good and bad.
But you do not need to completely disable the button, in fact, all effective
screen to teach the children, so not the
screen instead to flip is your
screen is not a very
addicted thing, playing games is not bad,
yes, but do not be obsessed with this position, how to
feel quite important.  That is, nothing at all, until he
has his own mobile phone he calls wildly, instead I would think the position is
that you have guidance to live he can play it does not matter, and at the same
time you say so that you hear actually more interesting things to
do right, I think this one position is I will me and my wife
.  The whole thing is one aspect you have to
balance, this aspect you have to create the environment.  I see that there are
many traditional Hong Kong parents, doing a lot of behavior out thinking it is
for the good of the child, in fact, it is convenient.  That is, for
example, I think you are walking around to make noise, I will
put a phone here so, in fact, it is convenient for themselves do not have to deal with the
matter is
a
day, Riji daughter left such behavior photos actually take time
, in high-quality time you give him
the phone actually he did not get along with you at all, so you
want to have a good relationship with you in ten years is actually very difficult, feed you children
after ten years
Well then you, or he is with some friends
, he went out on his own, so it is fighting that time here
, so but it is really not good right feed, that day there is a home
wife sick you have something to do, so you give a mobile phone to see is
not, not a fatal thing, that I think the
whole thing does not need to be that media very social media experience  There
is no need to go to the extreme of love is the best thing to do.  Being obedient or
obedient is not a compliment, do you want your child to be
obedient?  I rarely make my son obedient, because often the
so-called ઇ children are some smart children
, because he keeps challenging the bottom line and keeps doing
things that parents think are dangerous.  So actually that
child disobedient actually being a parent is very grateful, because your
son is really very prosperous, called stupid is actually very stunned, that is,
so he will not do anything dangerous, so he
became like very obedient, and this society.  I do not think it is
very appreciate good people, I can
flip and appreciate some, you know
where, you try to
challenge him under a reasonable situation, so so I will think I am very little earn
or obey.  I instead seem to now d often teach,
feed, you tell you, actually what do you think he does well
, he actually becomes you think he reads good right, you wouldn't say
, alas here you are very good, you read books all the time, I would
tell him wow here you read books all the time, you read what books you read lately
.  That makes the whole thing is concrete visualization
to find some, there is nothing in common.
And meat, I must have it, in fact, because it is a
relationship, it is the maintenance of the relationship, I think the most hope
is the colleagues, do not have to be like a child, and
waste so much money is not, followed and have to stink it every day,
is I think these my colleagues and better, so answer back to
say you only hire adults, because you will know how to
push away, in fact, you will know how to push away  You
can let him, in fact, Netflix said, that
his position is so you tell him you care he
cares he will feel he can trust you, can
trust you, he is willing to tell you, can communicate
Everyone did a great job on
this one.
Uh, now the bonus section, I actually I have that
thought about whether I enter this section, but I think alas
, very suitable yeah this time, is actually we
pre-all when this, Ah and told me that
, he actually because there is a middle school like this at the same time, he has in just
half an hour where I told me that one of the
things is actually called
smart, if you actually say what theor
Uh I also grew up with the Heavenly Cult, but
actually I did not believe on the road, it was until a few years earlier I encountered a
great experience I dropped out.  And you are.  When you encounter a
big one wrong section you teach instantly.  Yes um and
I found the common robbery we are actually and are the year, I think
it is a good, yes, are January Double 7 days of ji and his
birthday, actually I would like to say that is your
view of that bet that viewer, yeah why you
believe that I and my wife
more experience, in fact, that experience is to make us believe that when I
report to the hospital, because I came to the hospital this time
It, and the goods, then after, we walked to the hospital when we
asked my wife, as we are looking for the church to go back to it
someone, message me ra, my church has a
bureau, would you want to show up yeah this first.  The first was
I asked, that the hospital because my son built the hospital until a few
months, followed by that time I talked to too.  What if the children
die?  Parents are not believers he does not go to hell of this
Actually
he, that is you will ask this thing, his house fan blew open blew
Ը experience this wife, blow to her that article, that is that
chapter is that eh Jesus said to the disciples, feed the children
thank you for the daughter of heaven, because the kingdom of heaven belongs to them, wow, that is, that
time you think God seems to have
not seen anything to you, but I did not hear it personally
Speaking of words, but these experiences I am willing to believe that there is actually a
God, scare that you can say
唧, so of course can be, so but many mouths
while I would rather believe that there is actually a real God exists, that is, there is a
constant reminder is like a
God is watching us so he finally left the world
, but I think actually his life now seems to have a value,
I play
Yeah, you're lucky you're playing fusion this RPG
game are some people playing the
game like that, but are you able to best the
game, I think that's the biggest that difference
Yeah I'm next why eh, I'm in a life's heavy blow again
, I went another way, yes, I was
this is in 2019 so I'm
born after that, I recognized it
Hit it, very large, that is the most public
humiliation, nine years to build a business
, every day very hard work and heart, every customer day is
thinking, and then eh can 10,000 can be gone,
that is, the house in front of you tight you can only see, you can do nothing
after this, you also do not know how much burned is equal type that
suffering you can not say ah is burn from here.
Straight this step you do not deserve ah you
do not, I this kind of such scenario is falling on me when
I am coping, I finally decided one of the things
this is, I went to re-see my channel
when, I found wow, every video some people are bad.   And
then, subscribe fell, every
video, subscribe fell, which is
something that doesn't happen under the YouTube industry,
in an extremely anti-quality thing, but it happened
to me, how can I turn it around to do
better work.  If I'm tired of people saying it's better to be at that moment
, if I allow myself to accept it, I have money,
but I better, I will I will hate myself, I do not
let myself say this.  But this I because I have been religious from childhood to adulthood
.  And then I actually I thought in a moment if
I was praying
so but I was in that moment, I was struggling.  It is.  My good that
means I have something to come to see you on weekdays do not see you look for me to
have something to come to see you, I myself do not see let myself become one like this this
is number one.
Second is so if I arrive.  And then wow, it really got better
.  Of course I would be happy, but then I
began to enter into a doubt that I was exactly because I stood.
So so these results improved.  If I'm coming I'm going to have to use
everything I can to come to, improve or even have a
fight I don't know.  But I need a
no filter degree of no of a
data if this I, I think my move this
will confuse me um.  So I declare
I do not believe, anyway, in fact I have not believed it.  Um
I'm still worried that if I at the moment I did something do more then this
instead makes me do not know smooth.
So at that moment I did not believe in myself, simply that at that
moment you believe in yourself may not be able to do so, but
I have to let a no not yourself to go on
Think he loves you so you certainly won't, then you do not choose to come and run away now, that
is, I think the whole thing is very reasonable
, we all receive so Jesus Christ so strong is for people to
fake, but he returned so that for example, if you,
your master or I do not know what the name of the Catholic Church, in fact, he
said this listen to you ask for his kingdom ah, ask him secondly ask for something else
, followed by the last position, is I think the disciple, not
hope he changes the whole day of the market things expect that position is you to submit you are
willing to
pray to him
We won't know what the final result of winning more is, but at that
moment you get a high moment of calm, you have no hope of
believing that you have won, and to tell the truth, if you are now
19 years to you now this year six or seven years, in fact,
you look back and not can not pass it is a big challenge, but it
also makes you today another achievement.  Maybe
think your life must go through it.  The last
feedback is to be able to worry about the career is a
kind of happiness, because prove your own health is not a big problem, prove
your relatives' health is not a big problem scared, when your
favorite person in the hospital you YouTube fell or fall so
change account is so, because this
time no time to think, and the also went to place is really
grateful for everything, even when my son was away
During into, that see him did not see, scare me very grateful
, he did not suddenly report
rebelling him, that is, I think these are the
perspective of the problem, that
change
has different ideas, this will also recognize the first talk
when the challenge try it, scare you understand everything will pass, so
maybe your black able to clear your mind, to face that
challenge, I hope this challenge, I, grin
Is it to say, whether it should be believed or should not be believed ah, right
, I think actually R said is a good.
One thing of perspective.  Yes, these
rational discussions, yes, and I, I also I love that a
world out there is a conversation that can create pseudo-friendship
, but can actually very rationally discuss those
I, I myself observed that there is a price, is that no matter
what our choice is, we are reflecting that there is a certain
, I said I am not God because, and then I
believe I do  decision is a bent
must be removed how, nothing more than I want to choose mine is so my
.  At the same time yeah you will have your experience yeah, and then you
that moment when actually should have been Po will bring
you the greatest belief yeah, how you can live actually are
can make different choices at different times for the same
end.  It's me so I think it's not a rational
discussion, just we talked about actually talking about the position is mosquito
sun all the beliefs or so-called outside said superstition,
yes, I purely as a person to think developed a
scientist so he wrote out the box, the box is actually a
four grid, in fact, there is God you God and not believe God
You are God's word, you are so pious and respectful, you
won't do bad things. You actually have a good life, you
earned it, if you don't believe in God, but he has God,
eh, then you go to
hell
Get what you get, yes, so smart people, actually you
believe in God, basically you are no loss basically, yes
, but you are smart people, you do not believe in God, you have
several actually, that sometimes you think wow you match philosophers
basically did not say, but do not believe in God, actually chosen,
scare, that is whether you are what he refers to the people say, or that is the
end of your choice
Freedom of choice, is talking very bent if it is actually he
gives a space for you to choose, I do not think across the estuary for
a good letter picture, because I have many things continue to make
mistakes, and do not want to say in the high ground critical point, instead I
think everything is a person's own approach,
yes, you have to always remember that you are responsible to yourself, its and this
quite important.  I also saw you in the tree very rational and
time you also have very sensible, you have a very sensible part
, but also have a very empathetic part of so for an
outsider to see this, in fact, your sexual time must be extinguished his emotions frame
, but in fact we
admit that we are emotional
.  There are things we do for a long time and good things to do, in fact,
or we now do training all
talking about the value of things, is must be to understand the
importance of that value, say why the
trend is actually use, that is, a good
management, in fact, on the one hand to rational on the other to sensibility because
often people are not pure profit animals.  We
usually come to this section, I will ask each other a typical
question, is, if the death row
you are on death row, then, your last meal you will eat what so
eat what will react but the financial
example, I think it has passed,
You say yeah, you say I thought I genuinely have thought about you say you say
, I would ask you in return is can you not eat what, but with
whoever eats you die, what you eat does not matter is it the first so
I think this will be a want
so who will you be?  Best too, the child does not
realize the parents are there, the parents, but the parents saw me say death
stepping, yes, very moved is OK?
This often tells my wife, my wife asked me
what I want to eat, I said it doesn't matter what I eat, the most with you to eat,
she was immediately very happy.  That's a secret to this called husband and wife
very sharp ah, ah I didn't ask that question
between, he already knew I asked, han
.  Good
feel like nonsense, if you want to know then this is the mirror.
OK let's say goodbye here at 400,
thankyousomuch.
Thankyou.  Thankyou.
Thankyou.  drink.  You drink it all.  Drink it.
Feed here that is the last half only, talk or not teach turned more more.
People talk about us creative looking like a wife I really top you really
like a wife.  Now it is.  It's on the shelf,
clicked in after reading it Yeah.